<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="ajrotc_ribbons">AJROTC Ribbons</string>


    <string-array name = "army_ranks">
        <item>private</item>
        <item>Private</item>
        <item>Private First Class</item>
        <item>Specialist</item>
        <item>Corporal</item>
        <item>Sergeant</item>
        <item>Staff Sergeant</item>
        <item>Sergeant First Class</item>
        <item>Master Sergeant</item>
        <item>First Sergeant</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major</item>
        <item>Command Sergeant Major</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major of the Army</item>
        <item>Warrant Officer</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 2</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 3</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 4</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 5</item>
        <item>Second Lieutenant</item>
        <item>First Lieutenant</item>
        <item>Captain</item>
        <item>Major</item>
        <item>Lieutenant Colonel</item>
        <item>Colonel</item>
        <item>Brigadier General</item>
        <item>Major General</item>
        <item>Lieutenant General</item>
        <item>General</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="army_pay_grade">
        <item>E-1</item>
        <item>E-2</item>
        <item>E-3</item>
        <item>E-4</item>
        <item>E-4</item>
        <item>E-5</item>
        <item>E-6</item>
        <item>E-7</item>
        <item>E-8</item>
        <item>E-8</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item>W-1</item>
        <item>W-2</item>
        <item>W-3</item>
        <item>W-4</item>
        <item>W-4</item>
        <item>w-5</item>

        <item>O-1</item>
        <item>O-2</item>
        <item>O-3</item>
        <item>O-4</item>
        <item>O-5</item>
        <item>O-6</item>
        <item>O-7</item>
        <item>O-8</item>
        <item>O-9</item>
        <item>O-10</item>

    </string-array>

        <string-array name = "ajrotc_cadet_ranks">
            <!-- 15 items in total-->
            <item>Cadet Private</item>
            <item>Cadet Private</item>
            <item>Cadet Private First Class</item>
            <item>Cadet Corporal</item>
            <item>Cadet Sergeant</item>
            <item>Cadet Staff Sergeant</item>
            <item>Cadet Sergeant First Class</item>
            <item>Cadet Master Sergeant</item>
            <item>Cadet First Sergeant</item>
            <item>Cadet Sergeant Major</item>
            <item>Cadet Command Sergeant Major</item>

            <item>Cadet Second Lieutenant </item>
            <item>Cadet First Lieutenant</item>
            <item>Cadet Captain</item>
            <item>Cadet Major</item>
            <item>Cadet Lieutenant Colonel</item>
            <item>Cadet Colonel</item>
        </string-array>

    <string-array name="ajrotc_cadet_paygrade">
        <item></item>
        <item>(C/PVT)</item>
        <item>(C/PVT)</item>
        <item>(C/PFC)</item>
        <item>(C/CPL)</item>
        <item>(C/SGT)</item>
        <item>(C/SSG)</item>
        <item>(C/SFC)</item>
        <item>(C/MSG)</item>
        <item>(C/1SG)</item>
        <item>(C/SGM)</item>
        <item>(C/CSM)</item>
        <item>(C/2LT)</item>
        <item>(C/1LT)</item>
        <item>(C/CPT)</item>
        <item>(C/MAJ)</item>
        <item>(C/LTC)</item>
        <item>(C/COL)</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="army_ribbon_array">
    <item>Excellent Staff Performance Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadet staff officers for excellent performance.</item>
    <item>Service Learning Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who participate in service learning projects.</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Recruiting Ribbon - Awarded to cadets who recruit students into the JROTC program each quarter/semester.</item>
    <item>Parade Ribbon - Awarded to cadets who have participated in local community parades (Veterans\' Day Parade, Veterans Day Parade, etc.)</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>JROTC Athletics Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets that excel in ROTC athletics.</item>
    <item>Physical Fitness Ribbon - Awarded annually to the cadets who maintain excellent physical fitness.</item>
    <item>Varsity Athletics Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets that excel in varsity sports.</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Summer Camp Ribbon - Awarded to cadets for summer camp participation.</item>
    <item>Good Conduct Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who have demonstrated outstanding conduct throughout the year.</item>
    <item>Commendation Ribbon - Awarded to cadets whose performance of duty exceptionally exceeds that expected of a cadet of his/her grade and experience.</item>
    <item>Adventure Training Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who are members of adventure training type units.</item>
    <item>Rifle Team Ribbon - Awarded annually to rifle team members.</item>
    <item>Color Guard Ribbon - Awarded annually to members of the color/honor guard.</item>
    <item>Orienteering Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who are members of the orienteering team.</item>
    <item>Drill Team Ribbon - Awarded annually to drill team members.</item>
    <item>Proficiency Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who have demonstrated an exceptionally high degree of leadership, academic achievement, and performance of duty.</item>
    <item>Personal Appearance Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets who consistently present an outstanding appearance.</item>
    <item>DAI/SAI Instructor Leadership - Awarded annually to one cadet per LET level who displays the highest degree of leadership.</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>Optional by SAI</item>
    <item>LET Service Ribbon - Awarded annually to cadets successfully completing first quarter/semester of training of each LET year.</item>
    <item>Student Government Ribbon - Elected to a student government office.</item>
    <item>Perfect Attendance Ribbon - Awarded to cadets with no unexcused absence during each quarter/semester.</item>
    <item>Academic Achievement Ribbon - Awarded Annually to those cadets who maintain a grade of "A" in academic subjects.</item>
    <item>Academic Excellence Ribbon - Awarded to one cadet in each LET level for maintaining highest school academic grades.</item>
    <item>Distinguished Cadet Ribbon - Awarded annually to one cadet who exhibits the highest degree of experience in scholastics.</item>
    <item>Superior Cadet Ribbon - Awarded annually to one outstanding cadet in each LET level.</item>
    <item>Medal for Heroism Ribbon - Awarded to any JROTC cadet who performs an act of heroism.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ajrotc_knowledge">
        <item>Chain of Command</item>
        <item>Army Knowledge</item>
        <item>Army Rank/Rate Structure</item>
        <item>Cadet Rank/Rate Structure</item>
        <item>General Orders of the Sentry</item>
        <item>Army Values</item>
        <item>Uniform Inspection Check</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="army_coc_array">
        <item>Commander in Chief - Donald J. Trump</item>
        <item>Vice President - Mike Pence</item>
        <item>Speaker of the House - Nancy Pelosi</item>
        <item>Secretary of State - Mike Pompeo</item>
        <item>Secretary of Defense - Patrick M. Shanahan</item>
        <item>Secretary of the Army - Dr. Mark T. Esper</item>
        <item>United States Army Chief of Staff - General Mark A. Milley</item>
        <item>Commanding General,U.S. Army Training and Doctrine Command - General Stephen J. Townsend</item>
        <item>Commanding General, U.S. Army Cadet Command Major General John R. Evans, Jr.</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major of the Army - Daniel A. Dailey</item>
        <item>Command Sergeant Major, U.S. Army Training and Doctrine Command - Command Sergeant Major Timothy A. Guden</item>
        <item>Command Sergeant Major, U.S. Army Cadet Command Command Sergeant Major Kenneth J. Kraus Jr.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="army_values">
        LOYALTY - to bear true faith and allegiance to the U.S. Constitution...your peers\n\n
        DUTY - - to fulfill your obligations\n\n
        RESPECT - to treat people as they should be treated\n\n
        SELFLESS SERVICE - to put the welfare of the nation...before your own\n\n
        HONOR - to live up to all values\n\n
        INTEGRITY- to do what is right, legally and morally\n\n
        PERSONAL COURAGE - to face fear, danger, or adversity\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="ajrotc_army_general_orders">
        1st General  Order\n
        I will guard everything within the limits of my post and quit my post only when properly relieved.\n\n

        2nd General Order\n
        I will obey my special orders and perform all of my duties in a military manner.\n\n

        3rd General Order\n
        I will report violations of my special orders, emergencies, and anything not covered in my instructions, to the commander of the relief.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="ajrotc_army_founded">The United States Army was founded on June 14, 1775.\n </string>


    <string name="ajrotc_soldiers_creed">
        SOLDIERS CREED\n\n
        I am an American Solider.\n
        I am a Warrior and a member of a team.\n
        I serve the people of the United States and live the Army Values.\n
        I will always place the mission first.\n
        I will never accept defeat.\n
        I will never quit.\n
        I will never leave a fallen comrade.\n
        I am disciplined, physically and mentally tough, trained and proficient in my warrior tasks and drills.\n
        I always maintain my arms, my equipment and myself.\n
        I am an expert and I am a professional.\n
        I stand ready to deploy, engage and destroy the enemies of the United States of America in close combat.\n
        I am a guardian of freedom and the American way of life.\n
        I Am An American Solider.\n</string>

    <string name="ajrotc_cadet_creed">
        Army JROTC Cadet Creed\n\n
        I am an Army Junior ROTC Cadet.\n
        I will always conduct myself to bring credit to my family, country, school and the Corps of Cadets.\n
        I am loyal and patriotic.\n
        I am the future of the United States of America.\n
        I do not lie, cheat or steal and will always be accountable for my actions and deeds.\n
        I will always practice good citizenship and patriotism.\n
        I will work hard to improve my mind and strengthen my body.\n
        I will seek the mantle of leadership and stand prepared to uphold the Constitution and the American way of life.\n
        May God grant me the strength to always live by this creed.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ajrotc_all_knowledge">

        -The United States Army was founded on June 14, 1775.\n\n

        -


                Army JROTC Cadet Creed\n\n
        -I am an Army Junior ROTC Cadet.\n
        -I will always conduct myself to bring credit to my family, country, school and the Corps of Cadets.\n
        -I am loyal and patriotic.\n
        -I am the future of the United States of America.\n
        -I do not lie, cheat or steal and will always be accountable for my actions and deeds.\n
        -I will always practice good citizenship and patriotism.\n
        -I will work hard to improve my mind and strengthen my body.\n
        -I will seek the mantle of leadership and stand prepared to uphold the Constitution and the American way of life.\n
        -May God grant me the strength to always live by this creed.\n\n

                SOLDIERS CREED\n\n
        I am an American Solider.\n
        I am a Warrior and a member of a team.\n
        I serve the people of the United States and live the Army Values.\n
        I will always place the mission first.\n
        I will never accept defeat.\n
        I will never quit.\n
        I will never leave a fallen comrade.\n
        I am disciplined, physically and mentally tough, trained and proficient in my warrior tasks and drills.\n
        I always maintain my arms, my equipment and myself.\n
        I am an expert and I am a professional.\n
        I stand ready to deploy, engage and destroy the enemies of the United States of America in close combat.\n
        I am a guardian of freedom and the American way of life.\n
        I Am An American Solider.\n\n

        THE STAR-SPANGLED-BANNER\
        O say, can you see, by the dawn’s early light,
        What so proudly we hailed at the twilight’s last gleaming,
        Whose broad stripes and bright stars, through the perilous fight,
        O’er the ramparts we watched were so gallantly streaming?
        And the rockets’ red glare, the bombs bursting in air
        Gave proof through the night that our flag was still there,
        O say, does that Star-Spangled Banner yet wave
        O’er the land of the free and the home of the brave?\n
        On the shore dimly seen through the mist of the deep,
        Where the foe’s haughty host in dread silence reposes,
        What is that which the breeze, o’er the towering steep
        As it fitfully blows, half conceals, half discloses?
        Now it catches the gleam of the morning’s first beam,
        In full glory reflected now shines on the stream;
        ‘Til the Star-Spangled Banner—O long may it wave
        O’er the land of the free and the home of the brave.\n
        O thus be it ever when free men shall stand
        Between their loved homes and the war’s desolation;
        Blest with victory and peace, may the heaven rescued land
        Praise the Power that has made and preserved us a nation.
        Then conquer we must, when our cause it is just,
        And this be our motto, "In God is our trust;"
        And the Star-Spangled Banner in triumph shall wave
        O’er the land of the free and the home of the brave.
    </string>


</resources>