<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- <string name=""></string> -->
    <!-- info -->

    <string name="knowledge">Knowledge</string>
    <string name="rank_structure">Ranks</string>
    <string name="jrotc_ranks">MCJROTC Ranks</string>
    <string name="officers">Officer Ranks</string>
    <string name="enlisted">Enlisted Ranks</string>
    <string name="important_marines">Important Marines</string>
    <string name="marine_corps_info">Marine Corps Knowledge</string>
    <string name="general_orders">General orders</string>
    <string name="leadership_principles">Leadership Principles</string>
    <string name="leadership_traits">Leadership Traits</string>
    <string name="mcjrotc_ribbons">MCJROTC ribbons</string>
    <string name="rhs_mcjrotc_chain_of_command">RHS JROTC Chain Of Command</string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="pft_calculator">Pft Calculator</string>
    <string name="rhs_jrotc">RHS JROTC Events</string>
    <string name="title_activity_knowledge">Knowledge</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pft_calc">Pft Calc</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rhs_event">Rhs Event</string>
    <string name="title_activity_boot_camp">Boot Camp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chain_of_command">Chain Of Command</string>

    <!-- Chain of command people -->

    <string name="President">\nCommander in Chief-Barack Obama\n</string>
    <string name="vp">Vice President-Joe Biden\n</string>
    <string name="speaker">Speaker of the House-John Boehner\n</string>
    <string name="defense">Secretary of defense-Chuck Hagel\n</string>
    <string name="state">Secretary of state-John Kerry\n</string>
    <string name="sec_navy">Secretary of the Navy-Ray Mabus\n</string>
    <string name="commadant">Commandant of the Marine Corps-\nGeneral Joseph F. Dunford\n</string>
    <string name="assistant_commadant">Assistant Commandant of the Marine Corps- General John Paxton\n</string>
    <string name="sergeant_major_mc">Sergeant Major of the Marine Corps-Sergeant Major Michael P. Barret\n</string>

    <!-- Ranks -->
    <string-array name="rank_structure">
        <item>Enlisted Ranks</item>
        <item>Private</item>
        <item>Private First Class</item>
        <item>Lance Corporal</item>
        <item>Corporal</item>
        <item>Sergeant</item>
        <item>Staff Sergeant</item>
        <item>Gunnery Sergeant</item>
        <item>Master Sergeant</item>
        <item>First Sergeant</item>
        <item>Master Gunnery Sergeant</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major of the Marine Corps</item>
        <item>Officer Ranks</item>
        <item>Warrant Officer</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 2</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 3</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 4</item>
        <item>Chief Warrant Officer 5</item>
        <item>Second Lieutenant</item>
        <item>First Lieutenant</item>
        <item>Captain</item>
        <item>Major</item>
        <item>Lieutenant Colonel</item>
        <item>Colonel</item>
        <item>Brigadier General</item>
        <item>Major General</item>
        <item>Lieutenant General</item>
        <item>General</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pullups_array">
        <item>Pullups</item>
        <item>Push-ups</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- pay grade -->
    <string-array name="pay_grade">
        <item> </item>
        <item>E-1</item>
        <item>E-2</item>
        <item>E-3</item>
        <item>E-4</item>
        <item>E-5</item>
        <item>E-6</item>
        <item>E-7</item>
        <item>E-8</item>
        <item>E-8</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item>E-9</item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>W-1</item>
        <item>W-2</item>
        <item>W-3</item>
        <item>W-4</item>
        <item>W-5</item>
        <item>O-1</item>
        <item>O-2</item>
        <item>O-3</item>
        <item>O-4</item>
        <item>O-5</item>
        <item>O-6</item>
        <item>O-7</item>
        <item>O-8</item>
        <item>O-9</item>
        <item>O-10</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- General Orders -->

    <string name="first_order">\n1.To take charge of this post and all government property in view.\n</string>
    <string name="second_order">2.To walk my post in a military manner, keeping always on the alert and observing everything that takes place within sight or hearing.\n</string>
    <string name="third_order">3.To report all violations of orders I am instructed to enforce.\n</string>
    <string name="fourth_order">4.To repeat all calls [from posts]more distant from the guardhouse than my own.\n</string>
    <string name="fifth_order">5.Quit my post only when properly relieved.\n</string>
    <string name="sixth_order">6.To receive, obey, and pass on to the sentry who relieves me, all orders from the Commanding Officer, Officer of the Day, Officers, and Non-Commissioned Officers of the guard only.\n</string>
    <string name="seventh_order">7.Talk to no one except in the line of duty.\n</string>
    <string name="eighth_order">8.Give the alarm in case of fire or disorder.\n</string>
    <string name="ninth_order">9.To call the Corporal of the Guard in any case not covered by instructions.\n</string>
    <string name="tenth_order">10.Salute all officers and all colors and standards not cased.\n</string>
    <string name="eleventh_order">11.Be especially watchful at night and during the time for challenging, to challenge all persons on or near my post, and to allow no one to pass without proper authority.\n</string>

    <!-- Leadership Traits -->

    <string name="justice">JUSTICE - The quality of being impartial and consistent in exercising command.  </string>
    <string name="judgement">JUDGEMENT - The quality of weighting facts and possible solutions on which to base sound decisions.</string>
    <string name="dependability">DEPENDABILITY - The certainty of the proper performance of duty.</string>
    <string name="initiative">INITIATIVE - Seeing what has to be done and commencing a course of action, even in the absence of orders.</string>
    <string name="decisiveness">DECISIVENESS - Ability to reach decisions promptly and to announce them in a clear, forceful manner.</string>
    <string name="tact">TACT - The ability to deal others without creating offense.</string>
    <string name="integrity">INTEGRITY - Uprightness of character and soundness of moral principle, absolute truthfulness and honesty.</string>
    <string name="endurance">ENDURANCE - The mental and physical stamina measured by the ability to stand pain, fatigue, distress, and hardship.</string>
    <string name="bearing">BEARING - Creating a favorable impression in carnage, appearance, and personal conduct at all times.</string>
    <string name="unselfishness">UNSELFISHNESS - Avoidance of providing for ones comfort and personal advancement at the expense of others. </string>
    <string name="courage">COURAGE - A mental quality that recognizes fear of danger or criticism but enables a person to proceed in the face of it with calmness and firmness.</string>
    <string name="leader_ship_knowledge">KNOWLEDGE - Acquired information, including professional knowledge and an understanding of ones men.</string>
    <string name="loyalty">LOYALTY - Faithfulness to country, Corps, and unit, and to your seniors and subordinates.</string>
    <string name="enthusiasm">ENTHUSIASM - The display of sincere interest and exuberance in the performance of duty.</string>
    <string name="jjdid">The leadership traits can be remembered easily by the acronym:JJDIDTIEBUCKLE. </string>


    <!-- Leadership Principles -->
    <string name="prince_1">\n1.Know yourself and seek self-improvement.</string>
    <string name="prince_2">2.Be technically and tactically proficient.</string>
    <string name="prince_3">3.Develop a sense of responsibility among your subordinates. </string>
    <string name="prince_4">4.Make sound and timely decisions.</string>
    <string name="prince_5">5.Set the example. </string>
    <string name="prince_6">6.Know your Marines and look out for their welfare.</string>
    <string name="prince_7">7.Keep your Marines informed.</string>
    <string name="prince_8">8.Seek responsibility and take responsibility for your actions.</string>
    <string name="prince_9">9.Ensure assigned tasks are understood, supervised, and accomplished.</string>
    <string name="prince_10">10.Train your Marines as a team.</string>
    <string name="prince_11">11.Employ your command in accordance with its capabilities.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_marine_ranks">MarineRanks</string>
    <string name="company">Company Grade Officer</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cadet_ranks">Cadet Ranks</string>
    <string name="title_activity_general_orders">General Orders</string>
    <string name="title_activity_leadership_traits">Leadership Traits</string>
    <string name="title_activity_leadership_principles">Leadership Principles</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mc_ribbon">MCJROTC Ribbons</string>
    <string name="title_activity_uniform_inspection">Uniform Inspection</string>

    <!-- History -->
    <string name="birthday">Marine Corps Birthday - 10 November 1775 </string>
    <string name="Motto">Marine Corps Motto - Semper Fidelis - Always faithful in Latin</string>
    <string name="colors">Marine Corps Colors - Scarlet and Gold</string>
    <string name="emblem">Marine Corps Emblem - Eagle,Globe,and Anchor,
        \nEagle-Symbol of our country
        \nGlobe- Marines world-wide service
        \nAnchor-Marines Naval Affiliation</string>
    <string name="first_commadant">First Commandant of the Marine Corps- Captain Samuel Nicholas</string>
    <string name="first_landing">First Amphibious Landing by Marines-Providence Island in the Bahamas</string>
    <string name="mameluke">Type of sword worn by Marine Officers - Mameluke Sword</string>
    <string name="grand_old_man">The Grand Old Man of the Marine Corps - General Archibald Henderson - known as the longest serving commandant in the Marine Corps</string>
    <string name="red_stripe">Red stripe worn on dress blue trousers – “Blood Stripe” - earned by Marines who fought in the Battle of Chapultepec</string>
    <string name="chesty">Most famous Marine. Awarded 5 Navy Crosses – “Chesty” Puller </string>
    <string name="mascot">Marine Corps Mascot- "Chesty" the Bulldog- named after Chesty Puller</string>
    <string name="nicknames">“Leathernecks” for collar worn on uniforms years ago.
 “Devil Dogs” for bravery; against the Germans in World War I</string>
    <string name="nco_sword">NCO Sword - The NCO sword is the U. S. Army Calvary model which was adopted in 1859
and briefly carried by Marine Officers as well. When the officers went back to the Mameluke
pattern, the Army-type sword was retained for the NCO’s. The Marine Corps is the only service that
has a specific sword for its NCO’s.</string>
    <string name="qautrefoil">Quatrefoil - The quatrefoil is the cross-shaped design on the officers’ barracks caps and was
taken directly from the Army of Napoleon III of France. It was initially used to identify officers so
that sharpshooters in the rigging of ships would not fire on their own men</string>
    <string name="medal_of_honor">Dan Daly and Smedley Butler: Two Marines that each earned the Medal of Honor twice for
two separate acts of heroism. Daly earned his first as a Private during the Boxer Rebellion and the
second, as a Gunnery Sergeant during the Spanish-American War. Dan Daly also fought at Belleau
Wood during World War I as a First Sergeant. Butler earned his first for actions in Vera Cruz,
Mexico in 1914 and his second was for actions in Haiti in 1915. He retired as a Major General.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_marine_history">Marine Corps History</string>

    <!-- uniform -->
    <string name="dress_blue_a">Blue Dress "A"-Blue trousers or skirt with blue coat,
         with large medals above left breast pocket, and ribbon-only awards on the right breast pocket.</string>
    <string name="dress_blue_b">Blue Dress "B"-Blue trousers or skirt with blue coat, with only
        ribbons above the left breast pocket.</string>
    <string name="dress_blue_c">Blue Dress "C" -Blue trousers or skirt with khaki long sleeve button-up shirt
        and tie with tie clasp. Ribbons may be worn. </string>
    <string name="dress_blue_d">Blue Dress "D"- Blue trousers or skirt with khaki short sleeve button-up shirt
         and no tie. Ribbons may be worn.</string>
    <string name="service_a">Service "A"- Green trousers or skirt with green coat and, khaki long sleeve
          button-up shirt, and tie clasp.Ribbons are worn above left breast pocket. </string>
    <string name="service_b">Service "B"- Green trousers or skirt with khaki long sleeve
          button-up shirt, tie , and tie clasp. Ribbons may be worn.</string>
    <string name="service_c">Service "C"- Green trousers or skirt with khaki short sleeve button-up
          shirt. Ribbons may be worn.</string>
    <string name="service_sweater">Service Sweater- Worn with Green Trousers,and over the
              khaki long sleeve button-up shirt with NO tie, collar is place on the outside of sweater.The service
              sweater may be worn in appropriate weather conditions.</string>
    <string name="utility_uniform">Utility Uniform(Camouflage,Digital uniform) - Camouflage Blouse and Trousers,
          worn with issued combat boots,khaki "web" belt, belt buckle,and boot bands. </string>
    <string name="belt_length">Belt Length</string>
    <string name="web_belt"> Khaki or "Web" Belt - Worn between 2 and 4 inches past the belt buckle.</string>
    <string name="white_belt">cloth or "white"Belt - Worn between 2¾ and 3¾ inches past the belt buckle.</string>
    <string name="tie_clasp">Tie Clasp - Worn when using issued tie, centered between 3rd and 4th button on the long sleeve khaki shirt.</string>
    <string name="skirt_length"> Skirt Length- Approximates the knee, not to exceed 1 inch above or below the center of the knee.</string>
    <string name="cover"> Covers- They are never worn indoors. </string>
    <string name="uniform_check">Uniform Self Inspection.</string>
    <string name="blues_check"> While wearing dress blue A or B cadets must wear the appropriate ribbons that
          he or she has earned. The Dress Blue jacket must be cleaned of dust, hair etc. This is the only uniform that
          enlisted ranked cadets wear the gold enlisted ranks on their jackets, and officer cadets wear the bigger version of
          their ranks on their jacket. Enlisted cadet ranks must be 3/4 inches above the end of their jackets. Officer cadet ranks
          must be centered between the gold ega button and the edge of the jacket.</string>
    <string name="delta_charlie">Delta and Charlie uniforms(Blue Dress and Service uniform)- The Khaki brown button-up shirt must be clear of stains or signs of filth.\n
          Males must tuck in their shirts into their trousers. The long sleeve khaki shirt must fit the cadet\'s arm length.</string>
    <!-- Ribbons -->
    <string-array name="marine_ribbon_array">
        <item>Recruiting Ribbon - Awarded when cadets recruit other students into the MCJROTC Program.</item>
        <item>Orienteering Ribbon- Awarded to cadets who have participated in orienteering.</item>
        <item>Rifle Team Ribbon- Presented to the cadets who have distinguished themselves on the unit\'s rifle team. Can be worn with Rifle Team bar device.</item>
        <item>Band, Drum, and Bugle Corps Ribbon-Awarded to cadets who are or have been in the schools band/drum and bugle corps. Can be worn with the Band bar device.</item>
        <item>Drill Team Ribbon- Presented to cadets who are a part of the unit drill team in drill team competitions.</item>
        <item>Color Guard Ribbon- Awarded to cadets who make up the official color guard unit(s). Also awarded to those cadets who performed in at least 3 color guard events for the MCJROTC program.</item>
        <item>Best Drill Squad Ribbon- Presented to a drill squad that has earned a first place trophy during a drill competition.</item>
        <item>Distinguished Conduct Ribbon- Presented to any cadet whose conduct and demeanor are worthy of special recognition. </item>
        <item>Longevity / Fidelity- Presented to those cadets who have successfully participated in the MCJROTC Program for 2 years. </item>
        <item>Athletic Participation- Presented to cadets who are or have participated in any school sport.</item>
        <item>Superior Marksman- Awarded to cadets who qualify as a superior marksman during competitions, by achieving a score of 270 or higher.</item>
        <item>Physical Achievement- Awarded to cadets who have an outstanding YPFT or PFT Score. </item>
        <item>Distinguished Military Training- Awarded to cadets who have participated in MCJROTC Boot Camp.</item>
        <item>Arts and Academics- Presented to cadets who participate in Poetry Out Loud competitions or have their art shown in display.</item>
        <item>Distinguished Scholastic Achievement - Awarded annually to cadets who have maintained an “A” average in academic subjects to include
            MCJROTC Leadership Education and/or are be in the top ten percent of the class. </item>
        <item>Best Drill Cadet- Awarded annually to the cadets who have shown superior performance in comparison to other cadets in drill.</item>
        <item>Civic Service- Presented to cadets who have participated in numerous community service events, including Toys for Tots and the city clean-up.</item>
        <item>Non-Commissioned Officer Leadership- Presented to a cadet who has taken charge of a platoon as a cadet NCO, for a whole year.</item>
        <item>Officer Leadership- Presented to a cadet who has taken charge of a platoon as a cadet officer, for a whole year. </item>
        <item>Student Leadership- Presented to cadets who hold an elected office in the student body of the school.</item>
        <item>Outstanding Cadet- Awarded once a year to cadet(s)(2 cadets per grade, male and female) who has A. Consistent superior performance in all facets of the Leadership Education Course
        B. Academic achievement in the top 25&#37; of the class in all academic subjects including JROTC.
        C. Exceptional qualities of leadership, discipline, character, military bearing, and military proficiency.</item>
        <item>Scottish Rite Medal- Presented to a cadet who has encouraged and demonstrated Americanism by deeds or conduct through
        participation in extracurricular activities or unit sponsored community projects and has demonstrated
        exceptional dependability, character, self-discipline, citizenship and patriotism.</item>
        <item>National Sojourners- Presented annually to a sophomore or junior cadet who is enrolled for the next year, is in the top 25% and
        has encouraged and demonstrated the ideals of Americanism.</item>
        <item>American Veterans (AMVETS) Medal- The award is presented to a cadet for diligence in the discharge of duties and the willingness to serve
        school, community and nation.</item>
        <item>Naval Reserve Association Medal- The award is presented to a cadet in recognition of his/her outstanding service and dedication to the
        MCJROTC program, academic excellence and desire to serve the school, community, and nation.</item>
        <item>Reserve Officers Association Medal- The award is presented to a deserving cadet who has demonstrated outstanding competence in military
        skills and has contributed to the common good of the school, community and nation.
</item>
        <item>Navy League Youth Medal- This award is presented to an outstanding cadet in recognition of his/her professionalism and academic
        excellence and dedication to the MCJROTC program.</item>
        <item>Military Order of the Purple Heart Medal-Awarded to a deserving cadet who combines both military and scholastic excellence with strong
        leadership skills.</item>
        <item>Non-Commissioned Officers Association -Awarded annually to the most outstanding cadet NCO in the unit during the past school year. No
        minimum time in program is specified. However, the award must be made to the cadet NCO/SNCO who
        has consistently exhibited the best military bearing, personal appearance, deportment and leadership
        ability.</item>
        <item>Women Marines Association Award for Outstanding Cadet- Presented annually to one second year cadet who has a satisfactory record of academic accomplishment
        and citizenship and has the highest leadership education grades in the unit.
</item>
        <item>Daedalian Achievement Award- Presented to a junior cadet who has demonstrated an understanding and appreciation of patriotism, love
        of country and service to the nation. Shows a desire and potential to pursue a military career, ranked in upper 10&#37; of the MCJROTC junior class, and 20&#37; of the school\'s junior class.</item>
        <item>Veterans of Foreign Wars Bronze Medal- Presented to cadets who possess individual characteristics contributing to leadership both in and out of
        uniform. A minimum grade of "B" in MCJROTC, and a "C" in overall school academics. The cadet must be
        active in at least one other extracurricular activity or club and may not be a former recipient of the award.
</item>
        <item>Military Officers Association of America Medal- Presented to a cadet for outstanding academic achievement. The cadet must be in the top 10% of the
        class, have an "A" average in MCJROTC subjects, hold an officers billet in the unit, and be in the junior year
        of high school.</item>
        <item>Military Order of the World Wars Medal- Presented to an outstanding first year cadet who excel in both military and scholastic activities, be in good
        standing in all military and scholastic courses, have indicated a desire to serve the United States in some
        capacity, and have committed to continue MCJROTC.</item>
        <item>Daughters of the American Revolution Bronze Medal- Presented to a graduating cadet who is in the upper 25% of the graduating class in all subjects. Must
        have demonstrated qualities of dependability and good character, military discipline, leadership ability and
        understand the importance of JROTC</item>
        <item>Sons of the American Revolution Bronze Medal- Awarded to a Junior cadet who has exhibited the highest standards of leadership, soldierly bearing and
        excellence.
</item>
        <item>American Legion Bronze Medal for Military Excellence- Awarded to one cadet per school per year who has grades in all MCJROTC subjects within the top 25% and
        has demonstrated outstanding qualities in military leadership, discipline, character, and citizenship. Worn
        with the Military Excellence Device.</item>
        <item>American Legion Award for Scholastic Excellence- Awarded to one cadet per school per year who has an academic average earned on all courses other than
        MCJROTC in the top 10&#37; of the class and have grades in all MCJROTC subjects within th top 25% . Have
        demonstrated qualities of leadership and actively participated in related student activities. Worn with the
        Scholastic Excellence Device.</item>
        <item>Marine Corps Reserve Association Outstanding Unit- Authorized for those cadets whose unit received recognition by placing either first, second, or third in
        competition for the outstanding MCJROTC unit.
</item>
        <item>Legion of Valor Bronze Cross Achievement- Awarded to one Senior Cadet per District who has a MCJROTC class standing in the top 25% of their class,
        has a school academic class standing in the top 25&#37; and has most demonstrated exemplary military
        leadership. Worn with the Bronze Cross Device.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- pft calc -->

    <string name="pull_ups">Pull Ups</string>
    <string name="crunches">Crunches</string>
    <string name="run_time">Running Time</string>

    <string-array name="mcjrotc_knowledge">
        <item>Chain of Command</item>
        <item>Marine Corps History</item>
        <item>Marine Corps Rank Structure</item>
        <item>Cadet Rank Structure</item>
        <item>General Orders</item>
        <item>Leadership Traits</item>
        <item>Leadership Principles</item>
        <item>Uniform Inspection Check</item>


    </string-array>

    <!-- Cadet Ranks -->
    <string name="cadet_priv">Cadet Private</string>
    <string name="cadet_pfc">Cadet Private First Class</string>
    <string name="cadet_lance">Cadet Lance Corporal</string>
    <string name="cadet_corp">Cadet Corporal</string>
    <string name="cadet_sergeant">Cadet Sergeant</string>
    <string name="cadet_staff">Cadet Staff Sergeant</string>
    <string name="cadet_gunny">Cadet Gunnery Sergeant</string>
    <string name="cadet_first">Cadet First Sergeant</string>
    <string name="cadet_sergeant_major">Cadet Sergeant Major</string>
    <string name="cadet_second_lieutenant">Cadet Second Lieutenant</string>
    <string name="cadet_first_lieutenant">Cadet First Lieutenant</string>
    <string name="cadet_captain">Cadet Captain</string>
    <string name="cadet_major">Cadet Major</string>
    <string name="cadet_lieutenant_colonel">Cadet Lieutenant Colonel</string>
    <string name="cadet_colonel">Cadet Colonel</string>

    <string-array name="mcjrotc_cadet_ranks">
        <item>Cadet Private</item>
        <item>Cadet Private First Class</item>
        <item>Cadet Lance Corporal</item>
        <item>Cadet Corporal</item>
        <item>Cadet Sergeant</item>
        <item>Cadet Staff Sergeant</item>
        <item>Cadet Gunnery Sergeant</item>
        <item>Cadet First Sergeant</item>
        <item>Cadet Sergeant Major</item>

        <item>Cadet Second Lieutenant </item>
        <item>Cadet First Lieutenant</item>
        <item>Cadet Captain</item>
        <item>Cadet Major</item>
        <item>Cadet Lieutenant Colonel</item>
        <item>Cadet Colonel</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mcjrotc_cadet_paygrade">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>

        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="marine_coc_array">
        <item>Commander in Chief - Donald J. Trump</item>
        <item>Vice President - Mike Pence</item>
        <item>Speaker of the House - Nancy Pelosi</item>
        <item>Secretary of State - Mike Pompeo</item>
        <item>Secretary of Defense - Patrick M. Shanahan</item>
        <item>Secretary of the Navy - Richard V. Spencer</item>
        <item>Commandant of the Marine Corps - General Robert B. Neller</item>
        <item>Assistant Commandant of the Marine Corps - General Gary L. Thomas</item>
        <item>Sergeant Major of the Marine Corps - Sergeant Major Ronald L. Green</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_knowledge2">Knowledge2</string>

</resources>